<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Your awesome title</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 15:24:53 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 15:24:53 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>DevOps Engineer OpenStack Support</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;responsibilities&quot;&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Train to become an OpenStack Engineer at the expert level.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Work directly with demanding corporate customers.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Willingness to work time shifted schedules as required.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ability to automate deployment of OpenStack environments using Puppet and other DevOps tools.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Research and develop methods to improve performance, reliability and scalability of OpenStack in live customer environments.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Share knowledge with other team members and act as an internal escalation resource for other support team members.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Develop, document and champion new procedures and initiatives to improve system stability and performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;must-have&quot;&gt;Must have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Expert Linux system administration and troubleshooting skills.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Extensive experience with configuration management and deployment tools (Puppet, Chef, Salt, Ansible, Cobbler, MCollective).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Expert understanding of networking concepts and protocols (L2-L7, SDN, NFV)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of virtualization solutions (libvirt, KVM, Xen, VMware)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of distributed storage solutions (iSCSI, Ceph, Swift)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;definite-pluses&quot;&gt;Definite Pluses:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience with scripting languages (Python, Ruby, Bash)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience with Linux HA (corosync, pacemaker)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience with databases and message brokers (MySQL, Galera, PostgreSQL, RabbitMQ)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience with configuring, customizing, and extending monitoring tools (Nagios, Ganglia, Zabbix)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience deploying and developing OpenStack or other cloud management frameworks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 17:28:07 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2015/06/devops-engineer-openstack-support/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2015/06/devops-engineer-openstack-support/</guid>
        
        <category>openstack</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Software Engineer</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mirantis&lt;/strong&gt; invites engineers who thrive when challenged to help us provide the best OpenStack experience to customers. This position is within the Mirantis product engineering organization, and we’re looking for brilliant individuals who are eager to play a vital role in the intersection of IT and software engineering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re passionate about open source software, Mirantis is where you belong!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;responsibilities&quot;&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Proactively troubleshoot OpenStack deployments, detect and report issues&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reproduce customer issues in a local lab, confirm bug reports, provide detailed information to the development team&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Work closely w/ development team: discuss customer issues, suggest improvements, fix bugs in code, participate in IRC meetings, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Provide engineering support for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mirantis.com/products/mirantis-openstack-software/?utm_source=wwwmirantiscom&amp;amp;utm_medium=text&amp;amp;utm_campaign=MOS%20weight%20increasing&quot;&gt;Mirantis OpenStack&lt;/a&gt; issues escalated by support/ops team. Help support/ops team deal w/ critical customer issues, participate in troubleshooting sessions over Webex as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;must-have&quot;&gt;Must have&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Expert Linux system administration and troubleshooting skills&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Expert understanding of networking concepts and protocols&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ability to read and understand Python, Ruby code; basic scripting skills&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of virtualization solutions (libvirt, KVM, Xen, VMWare)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of distributed storage solutions (iSCSl, Ceph, Swift)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;will-be-a-plus&quot;&gt;Will be a plus&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience working w/ and maintaining large Python codebases&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience w/ Linux HA (corosync, pacemaker)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience w/ databases and message brokers (MySQL, Galera, PostgreSQL, RabbitMQ)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience with configuring, customizing, and extending monitoring tools (Nagios, Ganglia, Zabbix)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience working configuration management tools (Puppet, Chef, Salt, Ansible, Cobbler, MCollective)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience deploying and developing OpenStack&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;we-offer&quot;&gt;We offer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Work in the Silicon Valley w/ established leaders in their industry&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Work w/ exceptionally passionate, talented and engaging colleagues&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;High-energy atmosphere of a young open-source friendly company&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Competitive compensation package w/ strong benefits plan and stock options&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Opportunity to make a difference in the world of cloud computing&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Flexible schedule, lots of freedom for creativity and personal growth&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 17:08:07 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2015/06/software-engineer/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2015/06/software-engineer/</guid>
        
        <category>openstack</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Senior Deployment Engineer (OpenStack Services)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mirantis&lt;/strong&gt;, Inc is looking for enthusiastic &lt;strong&gt;Senior Deployment Engineer&lt;/strong&gt; who will be extending OpenStack to build enterprise-grade automatic deployment suite for IaaS platforms. We would like to find an engineer who is willing to work on intersection of IT and software engineering, be passionate about open source and be able to design and deploy cloud infrastructure built on top of open-source components.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;responsibilities&quot;&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Help Mirantis build world-class automation and management capabilities for the cloud;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Automate deployment of OpenStack and its components using Puppet, Chef or other deployment and configuration management utilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;requirements&quot;&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience in IT industry;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Excellent system administration and automation skills in Linux;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ability to identify and troubleshoot issues quickly in a Linux-based environment;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience of working with Puppet or Chef;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Good understanding of Linux networking;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Good understanding of virtualization;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience with bash and one other programming language;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of interactions between hardware components, operating system, and applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;would-be-a-plus&quot;&gt;Would be a plus:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Understanding of software development and release management process;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience of setting up and managing MySQL clusters;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience with HA and relevant tools, such as Corosync, Pacemaker, keepalived, HAProxy;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience with scripting languages, such as Ruby and Python;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience with Cobbler, or any other PXE-based system for bare metal provisioning;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Spoken English.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;we-offer&quot;&gt;We offer:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Work with exceptionally passionate, talented and engaging colleagues;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;High-energy atmosphere of a young company;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Really competitive salary and compensation package;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Strong benefits plan;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lots of freedom for creativity as well as professional and personal growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 16:08:07 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2015/06/senior-deployment-engineer-openstack-services/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2015/06/senior-deployment-engineer-openstack-services/</guid>
        
        <category>openstack</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>OpenStack Operations Engineer / Support Engineer.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mirantis, Inc.&lt;/strong&gt; is an American multinational company specializing in OpenStack platform and products. Our head office is located in the heart of Silicon Valley in Mountain View. We work for industry giants including AT&amp;amp;T, NASA, IBM, Dell, Intel, HP, PayPal and many more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have just opened a new office in Poznan and we are looking for &lt;strong&gt;OpenStack Operations Engineer / Support Engineer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;primary-responsibilities&quot;&gt;Primary Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Primary entry point for client incidents at enterprise level, managing live issues until resolution;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take ownership of operational incidents and handle escalation of issues, as needed, to development teams;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reliably work set “shift-patterned” schedule in Poznan, Poland;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ability to rapidly learn OpenStack projects via in-house mentoring;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ensuring customer success by providing a superior skillset with a strong sense of urgency;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Support Linux and OpenStack in both production and pre production environments for external clients;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Log OpenStack bugs with Mirantis engineers and/or community resources;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Contribute to OpenStack community via feedback and insight into chronic issues;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Updating of internal Wiki and Knowledge Bases for information sharing purposes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;qualifications&quot;&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An extreme focus on customers’ success;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fluent English, both spoken and written;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of operational concepts with focus on critical support;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Solid real-world experience with at least one virtualization technology platform;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Practical and advanced experience with Linux/Unix system administration and troubleshooting in enterprise server environments;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience in supporting large-scale multi-tenant infrastructure level services (load balancers, firewalls, etc.);&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience with supporting external clients at the enterprise level;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ability to troubleshoot the “whole stack” independently to isolate incidents’ root cause;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Familiarity with cloud computing concepts, including horizontal scaling;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Self-starter, taking initiative and requiring minimal oversight;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Willingness to keep abreast of rapidly changing technical environments and quickly evolving software platforms;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Willingness to work outside your technical “comfort zone”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nice-to-have&quot;&gt;Nice to Have:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Python, Puppet, and Cobbler experience are strong pluses;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;libvirt/QEMU/KVM experience;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Excellent understanding of data center organization, including hardware configurations and networking;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Familiarity with OpenStack, and the willingness to be trained to expert level;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Experience with HA solutions; HA-proxy, Pacemaker, Corosync;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Scripting ability in at least one: bash, perl or Python;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Familiarity with ticketing systems and case tracking;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ability to analyze incident trends and recommend solutions;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Familiarity with production monitoring and alerting;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;You are aware of the differences between a cumulus formation and an artesian well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-we-offer&quot;&gt;What We Offer:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Work with established leaders in their industry;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Work with exceptionally passionate, talented and engaging colleagues;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;High-energy atmosphere of a young company, competitive compensation package with strong benefits plan;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lots of freedom for creativity and personal growth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 12:08:07 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2015/06/openstack-operations-engineer-support-engineer/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2015/06/openstack-operations-engineer-support-engineer/</guid>
        
        <category>openstack</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
